Guide to the Woman's College records, 1928-1974 UA.25.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Office of the Dean.1928-1974
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 1928-1974 [Dc60s; MGW38-70; OD25-70; OD25-72; OD30-71; OD43-63; OD45-72; OD45-72; OD62-72; OD63-71; ODc60s; ODMF63-73; ODMGW33-69]., 24 boxes
    - Living-Learning Experiments, "The Changing Role of the University," (Southgate), 1969-1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Contemporary Arts (Epworth), 1967-1973 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Investigations into the Baroque, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Contemporary Morality, 1969-1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Correspondence and memos, etc., 1966-1973 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Current Trends in Theological Thought, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Edgemont Community, 1966-1970 (see also Edgemont Community Center, above) (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Environmental Corridor, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, French Corridor, 1963-1972 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, German Corridor, 1966-1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Harambee Dormitory (formerly Experimental Dorm), 1961-1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Humanities Corridor, 1965-1967 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Mass Media Corridor, 1968-1969 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiment, Omega House, 1970-1971 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Pop Music Course (Tabbard Hall), 1968 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Proposed Corridors, n.d., 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Science Corridor, 1966-1969 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Social Sciences Corridor, 1966-1969 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Society of the Seventies, 1968-1969 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Spanish Corridor, 1963-1972 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Urban Politics (Pegram), 1969-1970 (Box 35)
    - Living-Learning Experiments, Urban Studies, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Loewy and Snaith Report, physical development of East Campus, 1963-1964 (see also Arts Center and Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning) (Box 35)
    - Long-Range Planning, Departmental, n.d.; 1958-1959 (Box 35)
    - Lost and Found, [sale of items by student organizations], 1968-1969 (Box 35)
    - Luncheons with Student Leaders, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Mademoiselle" Magazine, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - Mail, 1951-1968 (Box 36)
    - Maintenance and Operations, 1952-1971 (Box 36)
    - Majorettes, 1964-1969 (Box 36)
    - Marriage and/or Pregnancy, Students, 1965-1968 (Box 36)
    - Mary Duke Biddle Parlor, pages from guest book, 1938-1950 (Box 36)
    - McGrath Report (Student conduct at Brown University), 1967 (Box 36)
    - Medical School, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Men's Student Government Association, 1964-1967 (Box 36)
    - Mental Health Service, 1961-1968 (Box 36)
    - Mental Health Services, monthly reports, 1961-1970 (Box 36)
    - Merger of Woman's College with Trinity College, 1972 (Box 36)
    - Methodist Board of Higher Education, 1965-1967 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous, clippings, programs, cards, memos, 1963-1984 (Box 36)
    - Morris Clara Elizabeth, [Woman's College secretary], 1970 (Box 36)
    - Mortar Board, National Council, 1944-1945 (Box 36)
    - Mother/Daughter Weekend, 1951-1957 (Box 36)
    - Music, Department of, 1964-1966 (Box 36)
    - Music Room, 1962-1967 (Box 36)
    - Naming of Buildings, 1956; 1965 (Box 36)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1961-1971 (Box 36)
    - National Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1950-1971 (Box 36)
    - National Health Committee, 1954 (Box 36)
    - National Merit Scholars, 1963; 1969-1971 (Box 36)
    - National Student Association, 1952-1956; 1962-1964 (Box 36)
    - Needlework Guild, 1931-1948 (Box 36)
    - Nereidian Club, 1954-1968 (Box 36)
    - News clippings, 1962-1968 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper, 1962-1968 (Box 36)
    - Non-Academic Employees, 1965-1971 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Association of Academic Deans, 1963-1967 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Association of Colleges and Universities, 1947-1968 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1942-1957; 1964-1970 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina College Conference, 1963-1965 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Personnel and Guidance Association, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - Nursing Education, B.S. in, 1953-1957 (Box 36)
    - Nursing Education, Committee on, 1965-1969 (Box 36)
    - Nursing, School of, 1964-1971 (Box 36)
    - Off-Campus Living, 1965-1972 (see also Studies and Questionnaires, below) (Box 36)
    - Officers, [various student organizations], 1948-1972 (Box 36)
    - Opportunities for Women, career, 1965 (Box 36)
    - Organization, Duke University, 1969 (Box 36)
    - Orientation Week, 1962-1966 (Box 36)
    - Orientation Week, 1962-1966, continued (Box 37)
    - Outing Club, 1955-1966 (Box 37)
    - Outlook, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Pamphlets, Programs, misc., 1938-1969 (Box 37)
    - Panhellenic Building, 1959 (Box 37)
    - Panhellenic Council, rushing rules and Panhellenic workshops, 1948-1963; 1966-1969 (Box 37)
    - Parent Fund Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 37)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1960-1971 (Box 37)
    - Pay Day, 1936-1964 (Box 37)
    - Peace Corps, 1964-1969 (Box 37)
    - Pegram House, 1940-1944; 1947-1948 (Box 37)
    - Persistence in College, 1937-1938 (Box 37)
    - Personnel Policy Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 37)
    - Persons, Elizabeth Anderson, [Director of Admissions for the Woman's College], 1971 (Box 37)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1952-1968 (Box 37)
    - Phi Kappa Delta, 1944-1962 (see also Phi Kappa Delta in the Student Organization's Scrapbooks and Activities series, below) (Box 37)
    - Philosophy Department, 1963; 1966 (Box 37)
    - Physical Education Department, 1948-1968 (Box 37)
    - Physical Therapy Department, 1963-1967 (Box 37)
    - Pianos and Organ, East Campus, 1956-1967 (Box 37)
    - Pickets and Protests, Duke University's Regulations on, 1968-1969 (Box 37)
    - Placement Services, Office of, 1963-1969 (see also Opportunities for Women, above) (Box 37)
    - Plagiarism, 1968 (Box 37)
    - Point System, 1956 (Box 37)
    - Policy Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 37)
    - Policy, Subcommittee on, 1971 (Box 37)
    - President's Club Room, 1963-1968 (Box 37)
    - Price, Dean James L., Vice Provost, Staff Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 37)
    - Privacy, Students, 1967-1970 (Box 37)
    - Professional Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 37)
    - Program Chairman, Board of, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Program Management Department, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Progressive Education Association, Eight Year Experiment, 1938-1941 (Box 37)
    - Project Bolivia (see Peace Corps, above) (Box 37)
    - Project of the Americas (PRAM), Duke chapter, 1967 (Box 37)
    - Proper Dress, 1964-1966 (Box 37)
    - Proposed Structure of the Students' Concern, 1963 (Box 37)
    - Provost's Report to the President, 1962-1964 (Box 37)
    - Psychology Department and Laboratory, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Publications Board, 1967 (Box 37)
    - Quail Roost Conference, "Undergraduate Education at Duke," 1965-1967; 1971 (Box 37)
    - Quality Point Ratios, 1957; 1967 (Box 37)
    - Radcliffe Institute, 1964 (Box 38)
    - Radio Council, 1950-1970 (Box 38)
    - Rating Scales, 1964 (Box 38)
    - Receptions and Parties, 1947-1971 (Box 38)
    - Recommendations to Administration, 1948-1953 (Box 38)
    - Recreation, 1948-1971 (Box 38)
    - Red Room, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Refunds, n.d.; 1963-1969 (Box 38)
    - Registrar, 1954-1964 (Box 38)
    - Registration, 1962-1966 (Box 38)
    - Religion Department, 1965-1966 (Box 38)
    - Religious Life, Associate Director of, 1962-1971 (Box 38)
    - Religious Life, Director of, 1930-1953; 1963-1971 (see also Reports to the Dean in the Reports subseries, below, for the Woman College's annual reports of the Religious Activities Director) (Box 38)
    - Religious Life, Director of, Job Description, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Report to the Chancellor Pro Tem Provost and Vice-President for Business and Finance on the Woman's College, 1968-1969 (Box 38)
    - Residence Requirements, 1964-1965 (Box 38)
    - Resident Status, change in, 1963-1971 (Box 38)
    - Rings, Woman's College, 1957-1973 (Box 38)
    - Roads Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 38)
    - Rockefeller Awards Committee, 1964-1966 [FERPA] (Box 38)
    - Romance Language Department, 1963-1968 (Box 38)
    - Room Preference Card, 1967-1968 (Box 38)
    - Rule Change Proposals, 1967-1970 (Box 38)
    - SAT Scores, verbal and math, 1960-1964 (Box 38)
    - Sandals, 1948-1971 (Box 38)
    - Sanford, Terry, University President, 1969-1972 (Box 38)
    - Schedule of Courses, 1947-1948; 1960 (see same title in Box 47, below) (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, 1946-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship Committee, 1946-1964 (see also Woman's College Scholarship Committee in the Committees series, above and and Scholarship Committee in the Dean of Freshmen subseries, above) (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, Correspondence, 1945-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, Donations, Campus Chest Fund, 1948-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, Financial Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, Fundraisers, 1948-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarships, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship, Publicity 1946-1950 (Box 38)
    - Scholarship, Alice M. Baldwin Scholarship Questionnaire, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Scholarship, Barbara Werner Scholarship, 1959 (Box 39)
    - Scholarships, Evelyn Barnes, 1953-1968 (Box 39)
    - Scholarships, General Motors Scholarship, 1966 (Box 39)
    - Scholarships, Panhellenic Scholarship, 1948 (Box 39)
    - Scholarship, William S. Lee, 1957 (Box 39)
    - Schuman Music Prize, 1964-1966 (Box 39)
    - Science Building, 1963-1967 (Box 39)
    - Secondary School Counselors, Conference for, 1960-1970 (Box 39)
    - Secretary, Duties of, alphabetically indexed, n.d. (Box 39)
    - Security Memos, Warnings, etc., 1969-1972 (Box 39)
    - Security Office Reports, 1960-1972 (Box 39)
    - Seminar Room, 1963 (Box 39)
    - Seminars, 1964-1965 (Box 39)
    - Senior Class Banquet, 1964-1970 (Box 39)
    - Senior Coffee Hours, 1948-1972 (Box 39)
    - Senior Projects, 1950-1959 (Box 39)
    - Sex, Psychology of, 1965 (see also Laidlaw, Dr. Robert, above) (Box 39)
    - Social Regulations and Activities, 1945-1968 (Box 39)
    - Social Science Center, 1965-1966 (Box 39)
    - Social Standards Committee, 1933-1966 (Box 39)
    - Social Standards Committee, Calendar, 1950-1967 (Box 39)
    - Social Standards Committee, CoEd Ball, 1961-1967 (Box 39)
    - Social Studies Conference Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 39)
    - Sociology Department, 1957-1963 (Box 39)
    - Soliciting Business on Campus, 1956-1971 (Box 39)
    - Sophomore Father/Daughter Weekend, 1964-1971 (Box 39)
    - Sophomore Projects, proposed, 1966 (Box 39)
    - Sophomore Symposium, 1966-1972 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, 1957-1966 (see also Panhellenic Building and Panhellenic Council, above) (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Alpha Chi Omega, 1948-1949; 1959-1961 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Alpha Delta Phi, 1941-1944; 1955-1962 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Alpha Epsion Phi, 1938-1944; 1955-1960 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Alpha Phi, 1955-1962 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Delta, Delta, Delta, 1941-1944; 1955-1962 1960 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Delta Gamma, 1955-1962 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Delta Phi Rho Alpha, 1949-1950 (Box 39)
    - Sororities, Expansion, 1952-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Evaluation, 1965 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Kappa Alpha Theta, 1941-1944; 1957-1962 1960 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Kappa Delta, 1938-1944; 1955-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1955-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Officers List, 1960-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Presidents, 1950-1965 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Phi Mu, 1941-1944; 1955-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Pi Beta Phi, 1940-1943; 1952-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Reports on the Second Semester Rush, 1946-1961 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Sigma Chi's Derby Days, 1964; 1971 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Sigma Kappa, 1955-1962 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Statistics, 1925-1969 (Box 40)
    - Sororities, Zeta Tau Alpha, 1940-1944; 1955-1962 (Box 40)
    - Southern Association of Colleges, 1963-1965 (Box 40)
    - Southern Association Reaccredidation, Self-Study Report, Woman's College, 1965 (Box 40)
    - Southern Association of Colleges, Academic Deans of the, 1950-1956 (Box 40)
    - Southern Association of Colleges, Programs, 1950-1965 (Box 40)
    - Southern Private School Conference, June 1967 (Box 40)
    - Space Allocation, office, residential, departments, etc., 1963-1968 (Box 40)
    - Speakers and Exhibits, 1958-1966 (Box 40)
    - Special Permissions for "Cutting" Classes, 1958-1962 (Box 40)
    - Special Students, 1963 (Box 40)
    - Spring Vacation, 1965-1972 (Box 40)
    - Staff Office, 111 East Duke, 1963-1971 (Box 40)
    - Statement of Goals and Objectives, 1964 (Box 40)
    - Statistics, Woman's College, 1927-1971 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, May Day, 1936-1938 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Office of, 1964-1972 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Student Christmas Dinner, 1963-1968 (see also Christmas Holiday, Reports, above) (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Student Council Plans, 1961-1962 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Student Requests, 1948-1953 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Suggestion Concerning Student Tensions [Overwork], 1947-1950 (Box 40)
    - Student Activities, Sunday Night Sings, n.d.; 1948 (Box 40)
    - Student Aid, Financial and Scholarships, 1932-1972 (for specific scholarship information see individual scholarship titles) (Box 41)
    - Student Deaths, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Student Employment, 1953-1971 (Box 41)
    - Student, Faculty, Administration Committee (SFAC), 1962-1970 (Box 41)
    - Student Forum Committee, 1939-1961 (Box 41)
    - Student Health Advisory Committee, 1957-1966; 1969-1974 (Box 41)
    - Student Handbooks, 1932; 1937; 1939; 1948; 1958-1969 (see also Handbook, Woman's College, above) (Box 41)
    - Student Organizations, Budget Summary, 1962-1967 (Box 41)
    - Student Organizations, Clubs, and Committees, 1951-1960 (see also Constitutions, Charters of Campus Organizations, above) (Box 41)
    - Student Organizations: President's Annual Reports, 1938-1953 (Box 41)
    - Student Records, 1962-1972 (see also Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), above) (Box 41)
    - Student Relief Fund (see Campus Chest, above) (Box 41)
    - Student Religious Council, 1949-1961 (Box 41)
    - Student Teachers, 1956-1973 (Box 41)
    - Student Self-Help, (see Student Aid, Financial and Scholarships, above) (Box 41)
    - Student University Relations Committee, 1967 (Box 41)
    - Studies and Questionnaires, 1959-1972 (Box 41)
    - Study Abroad, 1960-1972 (Box 42)
    - Study Rooms, East Campus, 1963-1970 (Box 42)
    - Sullivan Award, 1957-1964 (Box 42)
    - Summer Activities, Students, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Summer Session, 1948-1973 (Box 42)
    - Summer Session, Enrollment, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - Summer Transitional Program, 1969-1971 (Box 42)
    - Sunbathing, 1956-1968 (Box 42)
    - Sunday Observances, 1962-1968 (Box 42)
    - Superior Student, 1950-1965 (Box 42)
    - Suspension of Class for Various Events, Committee for, 1950 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "The New Woman for the New Decade, "1970 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Woman's Role in Contemporary Society," 1967 (Box 42)
    - Symposium for Centennial, "Woman and Contemporary Life," 1939 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life: A Commentary by Women," 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Ball, Dean-Elect Margaret, Events in Honor of, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Biographies of Participants, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Brinkley, Dean R. Florence, Events in Honor of, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Ahlander, Mrs. Leslie Judd, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Ball, Dr. Margaret, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Bree, Dr. Germaine, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Brinkly, R. Florence, 1962 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Bunting, Dr. Mary I., 1961-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Dulles, Dr. Eleanor, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Gilmary, Sister (Dr. Eileen Simmons), 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Hale, Nancy, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Hawkes, Dr. Anna Rose, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Horton, Mildred McAfee, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Kenyon, Kathleen, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, London, Edith, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Mead, Margaret, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Roman, Nancy, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Correspondence, Taeuber, Dr. Irene, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Guests/Speakers Schedules, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Honorariums, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Manuscripts and Transcripts of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Master Plan, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Photographs, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Potential Participants, 1962-1963 (Box 42)
    - Symposium, "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life" Sound recordings, "First and Second Saturday morning session, March 16, 1963 (Box 43, Audio-reel UA25050006-RR-0002, Audio-reel UA25050006-RR-0003)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some materials may have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
    - Symposium, "Women in Careers," (see Directions for Educated Women, above) (Box 43)
    - Symposium, "Women in Science and Engineering," held at M.I.T, 1964 (Box 43)
    - Symposiums, Duke, 1959-1970 (includes Symposium Committee) (Box 43)
    - Table, [Gift of Dr. Bryan Bolich], 1968-1969 (Box 43)
    - Tax, sales, 1956-1959 (Box 43)
    - Teacher-Course Evaluation Book, student publication, 1971 (Box 43)
    - Teacher's Accreditation Report, 1960 (Box 43)
    - Teaching Responsibilities for Administrative Personnel, 1966 Telephones, 1960-1972 (Box 43)
    - Television Programming - WRAL (Channel 5), 1964 (Box 43)
    - Thanksgiving Vacation, 1964-1972 (Box 43)
    - Tours, East Campus, 1962-1971 (see also Sandals, above) (Box 43)
    - Town Girls' Club, 1946-1956 (Box 43)
    - Town Girls' Room, 1949-1968 (Box 43)
    - Traffic Commission, 1949-1965 (Box 43)
    - Transfer between Undergraduate Colleges, 1965-1966 (Box 43)
    - Transfer Credit, correspondence, 1936-1952 (Box 43)
    - Transfer Students, 1963-1973 (Box 43)
    - Trinity College, Dean of, 1967 (Box 43)
    - Trinity College, Regulations, 1966-1967 (Box 43)
    - Trinity Deans, memos and letters, 1964-1966 (Box 43)
    - Trustees, 1960-1966 (Box 43)
    - Tutorial Program, 1965-1966 (Box 43)
    - Twirling Corps (see Majorettes, above) (Box 43)
    - Two-Campus Situation Policy, 1963 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Minutes, 1960 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, 1959-1962 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Subcommittee on Matters Relating to the Woman's College on East Campus, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Subcommittee on Matters Relating to the Woman's College on East Campus, Facilities, 1960 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Subcommittee on Matters Relating to the Woman's College on East Campus, Maps, 1960-1961 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Subcommittee on Matters Relating to the Woman's College on East Campus, Minutes, 1960-1961 (see also Olmstead Brothers Report, below) (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Subcommittee on Matters Relating to the Woman's College on East Campus, Olmstead Brothers Report. 1960-1961 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Colleges, Committee On, Subcommittee on Long-Range Planning, Visitation Program, Faculty/Administration, reports, 1958-1964 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Education, Beaufort Retreat, Sept. 10-12, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Education, Dean of, Report to the President, 1971 (Box 43)
    - Undergraduate Faculty Council, 1970-1972 (Box 44)
    - Union, East Campus, 1963-1965 (Box 44)
    - United Fund, 1965-1971 (Box 44)
    - United Nations Model Assembly, 1960-1966 (Box 44)
    - University Administrative Policy Committee, 1961 (Box 44)
    - University Council Minutes, 1952-1962 (Box 44)
    - University Council Minutes, 1952-1962, continued (Box 44)
    - University Counseling Center, 1959-1972 (formerly Bureau of Testing and Guidance; see also Testing and Guidance, Bureau of, in the Academic Dean subseries, below) (Box 44)
    - University Editor, 1964-1970 (Box 44)
    - University Faculty Senate, Proposed, 1946 (Box 44)
    - University History, general items, news clippings, 1936; 1955-1972 (Box 44)
    - University Planning Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 44)
    - University Policy and Planning Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 44)
    - University Schedule Committee, 1956-1964 (Box 44)
    - University Social Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 44)
    - University Union, 1949-1972 (Box 44)
    - Veteran Enrollment, 1961-1966 (Box 44)
    - Vigil, 1968 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholars in Residence, 1963-1972 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Barrenechea, Ana Maria, 1966-1967 (includes a 1/4-inch reel-to-reel audio tape of Barrenechea's presentation, Feb. 14, 1967) (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence,Belaunde-Terry, Fernando, 1968-1969 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Glukman, Marta, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Henderson, Julia, 1963-1969 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholars in Residence, Knauth, Josefina, 1967-1968 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Marshall, Dr. Dorothy, 1965-1967 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Rivera-Marin, Guadalupe, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Visiting Scholar in Residence, Useem, Dr. Ruth, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Vocational Counseling, 1948 (Box 44)